恐怖份子正密谋
(Jack) Right now, terrorists are plotting
暗杀总统候选人
to assassinate a presidential candidate.
我老婆女儿也被挟持
My wife and daughter have been kidnapped.
而我的同事 可能同时牵涉其中
And people that I work with may be involved in both.
我是联邦探员杰克鲍尔
I'm FederalAgent Jack Bauer.
今天将是我这辈子最长的一天
This is the longest day ofmy life.
以下是发生在中午12点至13点
美国总统大选加州初选当天的事
继续走
Keep moving.
尼尔 去小路拦截他们
Neill, cut them off at the service road.
其他的人去追他
- The rest of you, come up behind him. - lra...
你怎么会让这种事发生?
How could you let this happen?
我们准备在小路拦截他们
We're cutting them off at the service road.
鲍尔跟他老婆女儿，还有瑞克
Bauer, his wife and daughter. And Rick.
确定他们不会往回逃
Make sure they don't double back.
-我以为我可以对付他
- I thought I could handle him. I thought...
-别再想了
- Stop thinking.
(coughing)
我们得继续前进
OK, we... we have to keep moving.
-万一爸他无法... -你爸会没事的
- What if Dad isn't... - No, your dad's OK.
他说到水塔会合 我们就要这样做
He told us to meet him by the water tower and we will.
我们只要沿着溪就行
We just have to follow the creek.
走吧，快点
Let's go. Come on! Let's go! Come on!
-我办不到 -闭嘴，你行而且你要坚持
- I can't... - Shut up. You can and you will.
-我会耽搁你
- I'm slowing you down.
-没错，所以你最好动作快点
- Yes, you are, so you'd better speed up.
蹲下
Sh. Get down. Get down!
到底在哪里?
(radio) Where are you?
对，什么都没发现
Yeah. I got nothing.
我们可以走了
Sh. We can move.
(vehicle approaches)
等等，到这里来，蹲下
Wait. Come here. Get down.
妈，接下来怎么办?
What are we gonna do, Mom?
我们进退不得 到处都是他们的人
We can't go back, we can't go forward. They're everywhere.
他们从树林拦截
I think... we can catch the road further up
我想我们不能再走这条路了
where it cuts through the woods.
-爹要我们沿着溪床走
- Dad told us to follow the creek bed.
-我们实在别无选择
- We don't really have a choice, do we?
我们往上走，来吧
We'll go up here. Come on.
(ringing tone)
你要联络的用户...
The subscriberyou are trying to reach...
他们胁持杰克家人的地方
Hey. The property where they're holding Jack's family
6个月前就被 一家虚设的公司租出去
was leased six months ago by a company that doesn't exist.
我得去查税务资料
I have to go over the tax records.
-你还好吗? -杰克的手机仍然没有回应
- You all right? - Jack's still not answering his cell.
他有可能关机 以免响铃引起注意
Well, he could've shut it off to keep it from ringing.
也或许他出了什么事
- Or maybe something's happened to him. - Oh, look.
若说有人会照顾自己 那非杰克莫属
If anybody can take care of himself, it's Jack.
而且作战组很快就会到达
Plus our tactical units should be there soon.
行动由邦迪指挥，他很行的
Bundy's heading up the operation. He's good.
也许你是对的 我应该早点让葛琳参与
Maybe you were right. I should have brought Green in sooner.
因为杰克的家人身陷险境
You let Jack make the call
所以你让他作主
because it was his family on the line.
你还能怎么办?
- What could you do? - Yeah.
很抱歉，这件事发生以来
Look, I'm sorry. Since this whole thing
我想我有一点严苛
got started, I guess I've been a little harsh.
只是有一点?
A little?
好吧，或许是很严苛
OK, maybe a lot.
我一直担心...
I just... I've been afraid, and I...
不用解释，好吗?
You don't have to explain. All right?
你想谈我们的事 等过些时候再谈
You wanna talk about us, we'll talk about it later, OK?
-我只要你知道没什么事...
- I just want you to know that it's nothing...
-你带洁美的母亲来了吗?
- You're bringing in Jamey Farrell's mother?
是的，来接 她儿子凯尔
Yes, to pick up Kyle, her son.
在她见到他之前 我要你们先讯问她
Before she sees him, I want the two of you to question her.
如果有对保护派默
If she has information that can help
有利的资讯，我要知情
protect Palmer, I need to know.
-是什么因素让你这么推测?
- What makes you think she has?
-4个月前
- $300,000 was deposited in her bank account
有30万存入她的户头
over the last four months.
他们杀了乔治佛拉格摩
(Palmer) They killed George Ferragamo.
这场火灾不是意外
That fire was no accident.
我要先找毛琳谈谈 然后马上去地检署
I wanna talk to Maureen Kingsley, then go right to the DA.
等到事实弄清楚再去
Wait until you have the facts before you go off.
事实?佛拉格摩被杀 好让我当选
The facts? Ferragamo was killed so I could get elected.
-你并不知实情啊 -那又如何?
- You don't know that. - Then what?
我只是说，在任何行动以前
I'm just saying, let's take a beat, see how
要静观其变，谋定而动
we should play this, before we do anything.
只有一条路可以走 麦克
There's only one way to play this, Mike.
毛琳终究会捞到 她从业以来的大新闻
Maureen Kingsley will get the story of her career after all.
在找毛琳谈过后 我就去地检署
- David... - And after I talk to her I wanna see the DA.
-你不跟雪莉商量吗?
- Shouldn't you run this by Sherry?
-怎么?好让她说服我?
- Why? So she can try to talk me out of it?
她是你老婆
She's your wife, David.
这也是她的生活，她有权知道
This is her life too. She deserves to know.
-营区撤干净了没?
- Has the compound been cleared?
-好了，但计划有些改变
- Yes. There's been a change of plan.
-意思是? -鲍尔如我所料的找上门来
- Meaning? - Bauer showed up here like I said he would.
-捉到他了吗? -还没有，但我会的
- You have him? - Not yet, but I will.
恭喜你，艾拉
Congratulations, lra.You may have
你为自己创造了另一次机会
bought yourself a second chance.
契约规定是刺杀派默
My contract included killing Palmer.
我要事情做得完美
I wanna make good on it.
听起来，你似乎已经
The way you were talking, it sounded like
把这件事交给别人处理
you handed it off to someone else.
杀了鲍尔 然后我们再来谈参议员
Bring me Bauer's body. Then we'll talk about the senator.
我很快就会给你好消息
You'll hear from me soon.
Drazen?
我们要不杀了鲍尔 要不就毁了我们自己
Yeah. Either we eliminate Bauer or Drazen eliminates us.
-这是唯一的选择? -基本上是的
- And that's the only option here? - Basically.
干掉鲍尔并不容易
Getting Bauer's not as easy as it sounds.
他用手机 对外协调联络
He phoned in some GPS coordinates to somebody.
不管他跟谁联络
Whoever that is, I'm sure they're
救兵一定很快就会到达
gonna be calling the cavalry in soon.
我们不如减少损失 赶快离开这鬼地方
I say we just cut our losses and get the hell outta here.
光避开他们没有用
You don't just get out with these people.
他们会追捕你
They come after you.
不论躲到哪里
They keep coming until they find you,
不抓到你他们不会停手
no matter where you are.
而一旦他们...
And when they do...
相信我，干掉鲍尔
Believe me, killing Bauer
是我们唯一的生路
is our only chance of staying alive.
她们应该已经到了 过来坐下
They should have been here by now. Come here. Sit down.
小心点
Easy, easy.
让我看一看
Here, let me take a look at it.
好，这会有一阵子刺痛
OK. This is gonna sting for a while,
但你并没有致命的伤势
but you're not mortally wounded.
子弹虽贯穿
The bullet passed straight through.
却没有伤到骨头及大动脉
It didn't hit any bone or major artery.
-有没有不要的衣物? -有，在我后口袋
- You got any loose clothing? - Yeah, in my back pocket.
找到了
I got it.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
-等等，停下来，宝贝 -你还好吗?
- Wait. Hold up, honey, hold up. - Are you OK?
没事 我只想确定我们的位置
Yeah, no, I just... I just wanna check where we are. We...
我们可能有点偏南
We... we may have veered a little south,
但应该会碰到一条道路
but we should have hit the road by now.
我找不到 你那边看得到吗?
I can't see it. Do you see it up ahead?
你不清楚我们在哪 对不对?
You don't know where we are, do you?
Mom.
我们迷路了，是不是?
We're lost, aren't we?
不是
No.
我们应该直走
We should just go straight.
-应该就在前面 -你确定吗?
- It should be just up ahead. - Are you sure?
这有助于止血
That'll help stop the bleeding.
很好
That's good.
麦克是你的顾问 他有何意见?
Mike's your advisor. What's his advice?
他同意我的看法
He agrees with me.
他认为你试图接受挑战 是一个错误
He thinks you're making a mistake by trying to take them on.
-他们已掩饰了一个人的死
- They've already covered up one death.
-你并不知医生到底怎么了
- No, you don't know about Ferragamo.
但即使你是对的
But even if you're right,
让媒体炒作此事
will turning this into a media circus
就会让他起死回生吗?
bring him back to life?
-那不是重点 -你的事业，你的家庭
- That's not the point. - Your career. And your family.
你在放弃一切成果
You're... you're throwing away everything you've built
在缺乏事实 明确证据的情形下
without any hard evidence of what really happened.
警方会找到证据的
The police will find the evidence.
不，他们找不到的 因为卡尔跟他的老板
No. They won't, because Carl and the people he works for,
将会操控行政体系 达到他们的目的
they will twist the system to get the result that they want.
那是他们的生存之道 大卫
That's what they do, David.
而你将一无所有
And you'll be left with nothing.
亲爱的，你要有权力 才能跟他们对抗
Sweetheart, to fight these people you need power.
一旦你当了总统 你便拥有这样的权力
The kind of power you'll have once you become president.
一开始我们就知道
We knew from the start
这是一场艰难的竞赛
that this was going to be an uphill race.
但我们 快要成功了
But we're almost there.
看看民调
Look at the polls.
-雪莉，我想不通 -不，想想看，大卫
- Sherry, I don't know. - No. Think, David, think.
一旦你赢得候选资格
Think of the millions of lives you can
你就能改善多少人民的生活
make better once you win the candidacy.
我自己都不守法
How can I do the job
我哪有资格担此重任?
when my own house isn't in order?
David.
我叫她们在水塔等我们
I told them to wait for us here at the water
你有听到，对不对?
tower. You heard me say that, right? Dammit.
-你打算怎么办? -我得回去找她们
- What are you gonna do? - I gotta go back and find 'em.
- Green. - It's Jack.
-情况很混乱 -说给我听
- There's been a complication. - I'm listening.
泰莉跟琴并未到会合地点
Teri and Kim are not where they should be.
我要去找她们
I've gotta find them.
我得让救援队知道 去哪里接应你们
I need to let the team know where to pick you up.
告诉他们到营区的北区
Tell them to meet us at a water tower,
有个水塔的地点碰头
north area of the compound.
查看卫星照片 就在蓄水池上方
Check your satellite photos. It's overlooking a reservoir.
若救援队抵达而我还没回来
Alberta, if I'm not back when the team
他们会找到一个男孩
arrives, they're gonna find a kid in here.
-名叫瑞克，他受伤了 -他是谁?
- His name is Rick. He's wounded. - Who is he?
帮我们逃走的人
Someone who helped us get out of there.
-三个作战队正在途中 -还有多久会到?
- Three tactical units are on their way. - How much longer?
-10分钟，最多15分钟 -好，我知道了
- 10 minutes. 15, tops. - OK, I copy. Out.
- Jack. - What?
谢谢你
Thanks.
不用谢我 去谢我女儿
Don't thank me. Thank my daughter.
整件事情 我完全不清楚
This whole thing, I had no idea what was going on.
丹说我们只是要
Dan said we were just scaring
吓唬一些不守信用的家伙
some guys who'd backed out of a deal.
当你发现不对劲的时候
Yeah, well, when you started to see what was
就应当采取一些行动
happening, you should have done something.
但他是我的朋友
He was my friend.
你挟持了我女儿
Hey, you kidnapped my daughter.
这件事会让你永生难忘
You're gonna have to live with that.
孩子，想要重新得到机会
Son, part of getting a second chance
首先必须
is taking responsibility
为你所做的一切负起责任 你明白吗?
for the mess you made in the first place, you understand me?
那好，我很快就回来
Good. I'll be back in a few minutes.
(radio)
也许我们可以在卫星照片上
That shack over there. Maybe we can
比对那个小木屋，找出方位
find it on this to see where we are.
瞧? 我想我们不会偏离太远
See? I don't think we're as far off as I thought.
(voices)
Mom!
宝贝，身体压低
Honey, come on. Stay down.
走
(Teri) Go, go.
蹲下
Down. Down.
我是甘恩斯 每个人都去包围第5区
(radio) It's Gaines. Everyone circle back to section five.
当他到小屋后面的时候 我们就走
OK. When he gets to the back of the shed, we'll go.
-万一他发现我们呢? -不会有事的
- What if he sees us? - We'll be all right.
-你还好吗? -还好，没什么
- Are you OK? - Yeah, it's nothing.
-妈，你一直这么说，但...
- Mom, you keep saying that, but...
-会没事的，我保证，宝贝
- It's gonna be fine, I promise, honey. It's fine.
泰莉，趴下
- Mom! - Teri, stay down!
-你们都没事吧?
- Jack! - Are you both OK?
-没事 -过来
- Yeah. - Come here.
我是甘恩斯 是谁在开枪?
(radio) This is Gaines. Who's shooting?
不管谁开枪 立刻报出你的位置
Whoever's shooting, call in your position now!
他们马上就蜂拥而至
Dammit! They're gonna swarm this place.
我们快走
We gotta get outta here.
-瑞克呢?他还好吗? -他没事
- Where's Rick? Is he OK? - He's fine.
-他在哪儿? -在水塔待援
- Where is he? - Waiting at the water tower.
反恐组已派了直升机
CTU's sending a chopper.
我们要快点走，先等一下
We gotta get outta here now. Hold on.
现在安全，我们要快
OK, come on, it's clear. Come on,
没什么时间了
we gotta move. We don't have much time.
你好，瓦丝奇太太 谢谢你来
Hello, Mrs Vasquez. Thank you for coming in.
-他们说我可以来接孙子
- They said I could pick up my grandson.
-我们很快会带你去接他
- We'll take you to him soon.
-首先我们有问题想请教你
- First we wanna ask you a few questions.
-我也有一个疑问
- Yes, I have a question too.
一个女人流血至死
How can a woman bleed to death,
怎么会无人闻问呢?
and nobody does anything about it?
这事我们很抱歉 瓦丝奇太太
We're sorry about Jamey, Mrs Vasquez.
但事实并非如你所想
But it wasn't like that.
我女儿确实死了 不是吗?
My daughter's dead, isn't she?
请带我去见凯尔
Please... take me to Kyle.
我们务必 要问你一些问题
We really do have to ask you a few questions.
我对你的问题没兴趣
- I'm not interested in your questions. - Mrs Vasquez.
你女儿是个叛国者
Your daughter was a traitor.
她死前已经招认
- What? - She confessed before she died.
而如果你隐瞒实情
And if you withhold information,
会因涉嫌共犯遭到逮捕
you can be held as an accomplice.
要是如此 那么谁来照顾凯尔?
If that happens, who's gonna take care of Kyle?
你们想知道些什么?
What do you want to know?
国税局资料显示 你年薪4万5千元
lRS records show you earn $45,000 a year.
但有个你名下的户头显示
But an account in your name shows a series
一连串总共超过30万的存款
of deposits adding up to more than $300,000.
是洁美存的
It's... It's from Jamey.
这样凯尔才有足够的钱
So that Kyle would have enough money
万一洁美发生意外的话
in case something happened to her.
谁给洁美这笔钱?
Who gave Jamey the money?
-她从未提起 -而你也从没问过?
- She never said. - And you never asked?
这些钱全部在你户头
All this money in your account, and
你一次都没问过它的来源?
you never once asked where it came from?
凯尔需要你
Kyle needs you.
别做出任何不利于此的事
Don't do anything to jeopardise that.
麦克顿跟尼尔，只有你们
Maxton and Neill, you're the only two who
还没回报，你们在哪里?
haven't checked in yet. Where are you?
再呼叫一次 麦克顿跟尼尔
One more time. Maxton and Neill.
-我是麦克顿
- This is Maxton.
-你们在哪里?为何不回应?
- Where are you? Why haven't you called in?
我们正穿过溪床
We're crossing the creek bed,
要到小路拦截鲍尔
trying to cut off Bauer from the service road.
你们持续泄漏方位就甭想
Not if you keep telling me where you are.
把掌上电脑给我
Give me the PalmPilot.
只剩尼尔尚未回报
Neill is the only one who hasn't called in.
麦克顿，尼尔巡逻那一区?
Maxton, what area was Neill patrolling?
溪床的最北面
Uh... the northeast side ofthe creek.
他是单独行动
He split offon his own.
好，他们马上赶过去
OK. They're coming from over there.
我们可往下一点抵达小路
We can hit the road down a little farther,
完全躲开他们，走
avoid them completely. Come on.
毛琳，别逼我找旅馆警卫
Maureen? Don't make me get hotel security.
我知道你在里面
I know you're in there.
-你为何不见我?
- Why are you shutting me out?
-我想该谈的都谈完了
- I think we've said everything we need to say.
我至少可以进来吧?
Can I at least come in?
毛琳 拜开门让我进来
Maureen, please. Open the door and let me in.
我知道我曾要求你 别报导我儿子的事
I know I asked you to back off the story about my son.
但我改变主意
But I've changed my mind.
佛拉格摩医师已经死了
Dr Ferragamo's dead.
-你早已知情 -我不想再听
- You already knew. - I don't wanna hear any more.
什么意思你不想听?
What do you mean, you don't wanna hear it?
-我已经离开电视台 -什么?
- I've left the network. - What?
-什么时候? -你也应该放手不管
- When? - You should leave it alone too.
那是我以朋友身份 给你的忠告
That's my advice. As a friend.
他们找上你
They got to you.
他们付你钱了吗?
Did they pay you off?
因为我不认为 你会为了钱出卖自己
Because I wouldn't have thought you were for sale.
他们也威胁了你
They threatened you too.
-我会派人保护你 -我已经保护自己了
- I'll see that you're protected. - I have protected myself.
毛琳，你在隐瞒 重大罪案的证据
Maureen. You're withholding evidence in a capital crime.
什么证据? 佛拉格摩医师都死了
What evidence? Dr Ferragamo is dead.
他的档案也毁了
His files have been destroyed.
-但有基斯笔迹的文件...
- But the piece of paper with Keith's writing...
-没有那文件
- There is no piece of paper.
再也没有了
Not any more.
我仍然是这么认为 这样做是有意义的
There's still my word. It counts for something.
光有意义不够 参议员
It's not enough, Senator.
对那些人来说 是没用的
Not against these people.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
-没有无线电话机 -鲍尔一直在监听着
- There's no radio. - Bauer's been listening.
我们每一句该死的话
To every damn word!
1月份以后，瓦丝奇太太 曾收到两笔电汇
Mrs Vasquez has received two wire transfers since January.
都从一家在贝尔格勒
Both from a holding company
叫路卡优尼的股份公司转出
called Luca Univox based in Belgrade.
杰克建议追查 跟贝尔格勒有关的线索
Jack suggested a connection to Belgrade.
-两年前他曾被派往该地
- He was on assignment there two years ago.
-你查过跟本案的关联吗?
- Did you check for a connection to the hit?
这些档案 或能给我们新观点
These new files may give us a new angle.
在贝尔格勒我们知道有谁
So who do we know in Belgrade
是金融界的关键人物?
who's keyed into the financial community?
过来
Come on.
你能联络到他们吗?
(Teri) Can you call them?
或许吧 直升机现在应该到了
Maybe. The chopper should have been here by now.
-瑞克不跟我们在此会合吗?
- What about Rick? lsn't he meeting us here?
-可恶，没有信号
- Dammit. No signal.
瑞克受了伤，他在水塔里面
Rick was wounded. He's in the water tower.
当直升机到的时候他会出来
When the chopper arrives, he'll come out.
那我们在等什么?
- So what are we waiting for? - Kim.
-至少要让他知道我们在这儿
- Shouldn't he at least know we're here?
-等你爸说安全了才行
- When your father says it's OK.
-爸，这附近没半人 -琴，不行
- There's no one even around. Dad. - Kim, no!
快回来
Get back! Get back!
-是狙击枪 -我们怎么办?
- It's a sniper rifle. - What do we do?
待在这里，除了直升机外
Stay here. Don't move for anything
都不要离开，明白吗?
but the chopper. Do you understand me?
-你要去哪里? -他想要抓我
- Where are you going? - He wants me.
Jack!
他想要引我们 离开那些女人
He's trying to draw us away from the women.
那很好，他一死 其他的人就简单多了
It's fine by me. Once he's dead, they'll be easy.
我把他钉住，你去抄他
I'll keep him pinned down.
给他致命的一击
Circle around till you get a clear shot.
-该死 -没错，杰克
- Dammit. - That's right, Jack.
这么远 超出你的射程
You don't have a shot from that distance.
-我们还有多少时间? -是指什么?
- How much longer do we have? - Until what?
是指你的人马 到达这里
Until your people get here.
我要是你就会快走 而不会坐在那里等
I wouldn't wait around to find out if I were you.
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
我的老板交代得很清楚
The people I work for made that pretty clear.
(Gaines) Agh!
检察官在里面 要我进去坐吗?
The DA's inside. You want me to sit in?
等我1分钟
Give me a minute.
-长官? -没关系
- Sir? - It's OK.
他在竞选
He's with the campaign.
检察官就在大厅，卡尔
The DA's down the hall, Carl.
他在等我讲一个故事
Waiting for me to tell a story.
-都结束了 -我觉得一切才刚开始
- It's over. - See, and I think it's just getting started.
别耍我，大卫
Don't get stupid on me now, David.
-长久以来似乎我才是傻瓜
- It seems I've been stupid for a long time.
-那么就聪明一次
- Then open your eyes for once.
这整件事像个大的机器
This... the whole thing, it's one big machine.
而我是让活塞、发动机
I'm the oil that keeps the pistons pumping,
和车轮运转无碍的机油
the motor turning, the wheels spinning...
再也不是了
Not any more.
我喜欢你，大卫，真的
I like you, David. I really do.
而且我认为你将成为 全国最高统帅
And I think you would make one hell of a commander in chief.
我知道你 对佛拉格摩干的好事
I know what you did to Ferragamo.
每个引擎总有损耗
Every engine produces waste.
那是情势的必然
It's the physics of the situation.
-听听看你说些什么 -两者间做个考虑吧
- Listen to yourself. - Consider the alternatives.
从现在起1年内
A year from now, you'll either be promoting
你不是为国家向前迈进
your agenda for the nation,
就是到监狱去看你儿子
or visiting your son in prison.
-陪审团会相信那是个意外
- A jury will believe that it was an accident.
-我不是指那个强奸犯，大卫
- I'm not talking about the rapist, David.
我是在说佛拉格摩医师
I'm talking about Dr Ferragamo.
-基斯跟佛拉格摩无关
- Keith had nothing to do with Ferragamo.
-当然他不相干
- Of course he didn't.
但如果有人提到 "纵火"这个字...
But if somebody were to mention the word "arson"...
你这个混蛋！
You son of a bitch!
你栽了什么赃?
You planted something?
我们共同效力的那些人，大卫
The people we both work for, David,
他们懂得如何遂其所愿
they know how to get what they want.
嗨，麦克
Hi, Mike.
一切是怎么回事?
What was that all about?
检察官在那里等着 你要我怎么说?
The DA's waiting in there. What do you want me to say?
告诉他我很抱歉
Tell him I'm sorry.
我没什么事跟他说
I have nothing to say.
我犯了个错误
I made a mistake.
我听不懂
I don't understand.
我正在竞选总统 麦克
I'm running for president, Mike.
而且我将会当选
And I'm gonna win.
在这里
- Hey! - Over here!
Hey!
等等
Wait.
联邦探员，放下武器 把手举起来
Federal agent! Drop your weapons! Put your hands in the air!
-鲍尔太太吗? -我是
- Mrs Bauer? - Yes!
把手放下，你或你女儿
Put your hands down. Do you
需要医疗照护吗?
or your daughter need medical attention?
-不用，但我先生... -他在哪里?
- No, but my husband... - Where is he?
-我不清楚，就在这附近 -出发
- I don't know. He's somewhere up there. - Go!
跟我来
Come on.
跟在后面
Stay back.
Kim!
-鲍尔太太，等一下！ -没有关系
- Mrs Bauer, wait! - It's all right. Kim!
琴，别去
Kim! Kimberly, stop. Kim!
Kim.
-爹说他在这里，他人呢?
- Dad said he'd be in here. Where is he?
-不管在哪里，他们会找到他
- Wherever he is, they'll find him.
-万一甘恩斯找到他呢? -他会死
- What if Gaines found him? - He'd be dead.
他们会用装尸袋 带他离开
They'd be carrying him outta here in a body bag.
-他在这里，我得找到他
- No. He's gotta be here. I gotta find him.
-快别这样，琴
- Just stop it, Kimberly.
我知道你关心这个男孩
I know you care about this boy,
但我现在需要你在这里
but I need you to be here for me now,
而你爸需要我们 两个都在这里
and your dad needs both of us to be there for him.
你正在流血
You're losing blood.
还不足以阻止我杀你
Not enough to stop me from killing you.
或许我俩都不必死
(Jack) Maybe neither ofus has to die.
就像我所说的，杰克 我别无选择
Like I said, Jack, I don't have that choice.
那至少你可以 告诉我到底怎么回事
Then maybe at least you can tell me what's going on.
可菲 他曾提到贝尔格勒
Cofell. He mentioned something about Belgrade.
那是个军事行动
That was a military operation.
派默怎会跟它有关?
How's Palmer connected to that?
-当时你在，杰克，你应该知道
- You were there, Jack. You should know.
-说真的我不知道
- Let's say I don't.
我也是，我知道得越少 越能把事情办好
Neither do I. The less I know, the better I can do my job.
那就是我们这一行的本质
That'sjust the nature of our business.
那为何 要牵扯到我的家人?
Then why did you bring my family into this?
那也许是个误会
That might have been a mistake.
他们只是要针对个人
They wanted to make it personal.
"他们"是谁?
- Who's "they"? - (twigs crack)
放下武器，甘先生 我们可以保护你
Put down the weapon, Mr Gaines. We can protect you.
不，你们不行
No, you can't.
放下武器
Put down the weapon!
祝你好运
Good luck.
联邦探员！放下武器
Federal agent! Drop your weapon!
举起手交握在脑后
lnterlace your fingers behind your head.
长官，鲍尔正被我们看管
Sir, we have Bauer in custody.
另有一人已死亡
We also have another man down.
-马上带鲍尔到降落区来
- Bring Bauer to the landing zone right away.
-知道了，带他进来
- Roger. Bringing him in.
(helicopter overhead)
甜心
- Sweetheart? - Jack!
感谢老天！你平安无事
- Oh! - Oh, thank God you're OK!
-你还好吗? -很好
- Oh, thank God. - Are you all right?
-恶梦终于结束了，对不对?
- Yeah. This nightmare's finally over, right?
-没错，我保证
- Yes. Yes, I promise.
OK.
鲍尔探员 直升机正等着你
Agent Bauer, the chopper's waiting for you.
我家人刚历险归来 我希望她们能跟我一道
My family's been through hell. I want them to fly with me.
没问题，走吧
- That'll be fine. Come on. - OK.
甜心，把这穿上
- Sweetheart, put this on. - OK.
杰克跟他的家人已获救
Jack and his family were rescued.
10分钟内会抵达这里
They should be here in 10 minutes.
是好消息，但其他事情得加快脚步，
Good news. But we need to move fast on
洁美母亲提供线索
something else. A lead from Jamey's mom.
-钱从哪里来? -一个海外银行帐户
- Where was the money from? - An offshore bank account.
我们循线找到贝尔格勒
- We traced the funds to Belgrade. - Belgrade?
在我向你报告之前 得提升对派默的威胁评估
Before I tell you, upgrade the threat assessment on Palmer.
-你必须给我更多的...
- You need to give me more than that...
-同一个帐户显示有笔资金
- The same account shows a transfer of funds
转帐到 贝尔格勒的杀手
to an assassin based in Belgrade.
那是旧闻 就是那摄影师
That's old news. The photographer.
不，我们当地的线民回报
No. Our contact over there says
杀手今天早上才离开南斯拉夫
this assassin left Yugoslavia this morning.
也就是说 他可能已经到这里了
Which means he's probably already here.
第二个杀手
- A second hitter. - Mm-hm.
Merge: Sunpiny